<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.kodi.tts"
       name="Kodi Screen Reader"
       version="2.0.3~alpha5"
       provider-name="Frank Feuerbacher (fbacher), Rick Phillips (ruuk), pvagner">
   <debugging>true</debugging>
   <requires>
      <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.1"/>
      <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.1"/>
      <import addon="script.module.pydevd" version="4.4.0" optional="true"/>
      <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.16.0+matrix.1"/>
      <import addon="script.module.langcodes" version="3.4.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.31.0"/>
      <import addon="script.module.typing_extensions" version="4.7.1"/>
   </requires>
   <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/service.py" start="login"/>

   <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
      <news>Fifth alpha for second incarnation 2.0.5</news>
      <assets>
         <icon>icon.png</icon>
      </assets>
      <platform>linux windows-x86_64</platform>
      <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
      <summary lang="en_GB">
         Kodi TTS provides voicing of currently focused text, or through a simple API.
      </summary>
      <description>
         Kodi TTS provides voicing of currently focused text. It works with multiple TTS
         engines which is currently limited to GoogleTTS and eSpeak-NG (on Linux and Windows)
         as well as Windows Narrator (on Windows). Google TTS requires 'mpv' player to
         be installed.

         Kodi TTS has its own configuration dialogs which support voicing of changes as they
         are made. The traditional addon configuration dialog is NEARLY USELESS at this time.
         A limited number of basic items will be added back, but primary configuration is done
         by pressing Ctrl-F12 (configurable).

         To get started, read SETUP.md as well as README.md and RELEASE_NODES.md.
      </description>
      <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=357602</forum>
      <source>https://github.com/fbacher/service.kodi.tts</source>
      <disclaimer lang="en_GB">
         This is ALPHA quality.
         Limitations:
            For the foreseable future only Linux and Windows are supported.
            At this time Google TTS best supports multiple languages, however language testing
            has been very limited. eSpeak and Narrator are both capable of multiple languages,
            however a small amount of plumbing needs to be added for Narrator. eSpeak is a bit
            more complicated to configure so will take more time to implement.
            Slave-mode, which improves responsiveness, will not be available on Windows until
            it's Python is upgraded, which appears to be targeted for the next release.

         Feel free to use this service. For information visit the forum, above or
         https://github.com/fbacher/service.kodi.tts
      </disclaimer>
      <website>https://github.com/fbacher/service.kodi.tts</website>
   </extension>
</addon>
